Justice knows no borders
The Equalizer 3 is a action, thriller, crime film directed by Antoine Fuqua.
Robert McCall finds himself at home in Southern Italy but he discovers
his friends are under the control of local crime bosses.
As events turn deadly, McCall knows what he has to do: become
his friends' protector by taking on the mafia.
Robert McCall, played by Denzel Washington.
Emma Collins, played by Dakota Fanning.
Gio Bonucci, played by Eugenio Mastrandrea.
Frank Conroy, played by David Denman.
Aminah, played by Gaia Scodellaro.
Enzo Arisio, played by Remo Girone.
The Equalizer 3 is a 2023 American vigilante
action-thriller film directed by Antoine Fuqua.
It is a sequel to The Equalizer 2 and is the third installment of The Equalizer film
series, which is based on the television series of the same name.
The film stars Denzel Washington, reprising his role as retired U.S.
Marine and DIA officer Robert McCall.
Dakota Fanning, Eugenio Mastrandrea, David Denman, Gaia
Scodellaro, and Remo Girone play supporting roles.
In the film, McCall discovers that his new friends in a small town in Southern Italy are
intimidated by Camorra members and sets out to save them from the threat.
Talks over a third entry to the franchise began following the
release of The Equalizer 2 on August 2, 2018.
Following a long delay due to the COVID-19 pandemic, the
project was officially announced in January 2022.
Filming took place in Italy, concluding in January 2023.
The Equalizer 3 was released in the United States on
September 1, 2023, by Sony Pictures Releasing.
The film received generally positive reviews from critics.
A fourth and fifth film are in development.
The film explores themes of italy, investigation,
organized crime, vigilante justice, dramatic.
The tone is dark and intense.